Using language. Reading. Futuriscope. Excitement and learning.
Last week I took a journey deep into space to the end of the solar system and was pulled
Then I took a trip to Brazil and experienced surviving an airplane crash in the jungle.
After that, I joined some divers and went to the bottom of the ocean to see strange blind creatures
that have never seen sunlight.
For a break, I took part in some car racing and then skied down some of the most difficult mountains in the world.
I ended my travels by meeting face to face with a dinosaur,
the terrible T-Rex, and survived the experience!
This science and technology-based theme park in France uses the most advanced technology.
Visitors can get close to parts of the world they have never experienced,
going to the bottom of the ocean,
flying through the jungle or visiting the edges of the solar system.
The amazing, up-to-date information together with many opportunities
for hands-on learning makes the world come to life in a completely new way
for visitors.
I bought tickets for myself and my friends at the park's entrance,
but tickets are also available online.
Come ready to walk a lot - be sure to wear some comfortable sneakers or other walking shoes!